A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005) FA491
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2005.011: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2005; AC.2005.011; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3713-R3716.
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2005.011.7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AS 9928 - THANGATA, PAULANCO HOWARD - AGROFORESTRY ADOPTION IN MALAWI, 1999-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9931 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - DROUGHT STRESS TOLERANCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9938 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - GLOBAL WEATHER DATABASES: MARKSIM, 1999-2001 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9943 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA} - COVER CROPS INFORMATION AND SEED EXCHANGE CENTER FOR AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3716)
    - AS 9946 - AFRICARE - SOYBEAN PROMOTION BY SMALLHOLDER FARMERS IN ZIMBABWE, 1999-2002 (Box R3716)
  - BD, AC.2005.011.8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - BD 9619 - REAL MOVIES, INC. - FAMILY STORIES DOCUMENTARY, 1995-2001 (Box R3716)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2005.011.9; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - EO 9902 - INSTITUTE FOR PUBLIC POLICY RESEARCH (ENGLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: DILEMMAS OF GLOBALIZATION, 1998-2000 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9905 - STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK (ALBANY) - IMPACT OF WELFARE REFORM ON COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION, 1998-2001 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9913 - GREATER JAMAICA DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION - RELATION OF CULTURAL AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AT NEIGHBORHOOD LEVEL, 1999-2001 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9923 - NEW ORLEANS INTERFAITH SPONSORING COMMITTEE - COMMUNITY ORGANIZING INSTITUTE PILOT PROJECT FOR STUDENTS, 1999 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9927 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND (COLLEGE PARK) - CIVIL SOCIETY/COMMUNITY-BUILDING INITIATIVE, 1999-2004 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9930 - FUND FOR THE CITY OF NEW YORK - BOSTON JOBS PROJECT, 1999-2001 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9932 - LOUGHBOROUGH UNIVERSITY (ENGLAND) - WELFARE TO WORK POLICY AND THE UNITED KINGDOM, 1999-2004 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9940 - TOMAS RIVERA POLICY INSTITUTE - LATINO VOTER MOBILIZATION STUDY, 1999-2002 (Box R3716)
    - EO 9921 - GEORGIA CAMPAIGN FOR ADOLESCENT PREGNANCY PREVENTION - EVALUATION OF CAMPAIGN'S WORK IN THREE COMMUNITIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3716)
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2005.011.10; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GE 9803 - BEN-GURION UNIVERSITY OF THE NEGEV (ISRAEL) - PROGRAM TO COMBAT DESERTIFICATION IN AFRICA AND ASIA, 1998-2002 (Box R3716)
- AC.2005.019: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2005; AC.2005.019; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3717-R3719.
  - Global Environment (GE), AC.2005.019.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GE 9814 - CENTRE FOR SCIENCE AND ENVIRONMENT (INDIA) - REPORT ON GLOBAL ENVIRONMENTAL NEGOTIATIONS, 1998-2002 (Box R3717)
    - GE 9818 - FRIENDS OF THE CITY AND COUNTY OF HONOLULU - MAYORS' ASIA-PACIFIC ENVIRONMENTAL SUMMIT, 1998-1999 (Box R3717)
    - GE 9819 - COSTA RICAN FOUNDATION FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT - ELECTRIC VEHICLES, 1998-2005 (Box R3717)
  - Global Engagement (GEE), AC.2005.019.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GEE 9801 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - BC CONFERENCE: GLOBALIZATION AND HUMAN DEVELOPMENT, 1998-2003 (Box R3717)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2005.019.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GP 9910 - WORLDSPACE FOUNDATION - RADIO LEARNING CHANNELS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3717)
    - GP 9915 - CONCORDIA UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - PRESERVING ARCHIVES OF KARL POLANYI, 1999-2001 (Box R3717)
    - GP 9918 - WASHINGTON MEDIA ASSOCIATES - TV SERIES ON MEANING OF, AND LESSONS TO BE LEARNED FROM THE COLD WAR, 1999-2001 (Box R3717)
    - GP 9922 - FUTURE GENERATIONS - ENVIRONMENTAL SECURITY IN ARUNACHAL PRADESH, INDIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3717)
    - GP 9924 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - EDUCATING CONGRESS ON ENVIRONMENT ISSUES, 1999-2002 (Box R3717)
    - GP 9938 - AFRICANET TRUST (SENEGAL) - TWO TV AND RADIO PROGRAMS: TEENZINE AFRICA AND AFRICA THIS WEEK, 1999-2003 (Box R3717)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2005.019.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - HS 9214 - ZIMBABWE MINISTRY OF PUBLIC HEALTH - CURRICULUM PLANNING FOR THE PUBLIC HEALTH TRAINING PROGRAM, 1991-1992 (Box R3718)
    - HS 9512 - BOSTON UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE: URBAN HEALTH CHALLENGES FOR THE 21ST CENTURY, 1995-1998 (Box R3718)
    - HS 9719 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - SECOND GLOBAL FORUM FOR HEALTH RESEARCH, 1997-1998 (Box R3718)
    - HS 9801 - (HEALTH SCIENCES) - BC TEAM: LONGITUDINAL COMMUNITY-BASED HEALTH RESEARCH, 1997-1998 (Box R3718)
    - HS 9804 - (HEALTH SCIENCES) - BC TEAM: UNDERSTANDING SOCIETY AND HEALTH INTERFACE, 1997-1998 (Box R3718)
    - HS 9807 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: HEALTHY AGING, 1998-2004 (Box R3718)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2005.019.5; 2.63 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9730 - COUNCIL ON FOREIGN RELATIONS - COMMUNICATIONS WITH NORTH KOREA, 1997-2001 (Box R3718)
    - IS 9804 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE: VIETNAM WAR: ITS HISTORY, HISTORIOGRAPHY, AND LESSONS, 1997-2000 (Box R3718)
    - IS 9835 - CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF DEVELOPING SOCIETIES (INDIA) - ELECTRONIC DATA COLLECTION AND ANALYSIS RELATING TO NUCLEAR NONPROLIFERATION, 1996-2002 (Box R3719)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2005.019.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9810 - UNITED NATIONS POPULATION FUND - BC CONFERENCE: CONTRACEPTIVE COMMODITIES: EXPANDING OPPORTUNITIES FOR COMMERCIAL SECTOR, 1997-2001 (Box R3719)
    - PS 9822 - INTERNATIONAL PEACE MATERNITY AND CHILD HEALTH HOSPITAL (CHINA) - PROBABILITY OF CONCEPTION IN CHINESE WOMEN, 1998-2003 (Box R3719)
    - PS 9824 - INTERNATIONAL AGENCY FOR RESEARCH ON CANCER, WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (FRANCE) - CO-FACTORS FOR CERVICAL CANCER, 1997-2002 (Box R3719)
    - PS 9909 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - FOLLOW-UP TO CHINESE STATE FAMILY PLANNING COMMISSION PROJECT, 1999-2005 (Box R3719)
    - PS 9910 - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH TECHNOLOGIES PROJECT - COMMUNICATI ON BETWEEN INDUSTRY AND ADVOCATES, 1998-2001 (Box R3719)
    - PS 9911 - PARLIAMENTARIANS FOR GLOBAL ACTION - WEST AFRICAN INITIATIVE ON POPULATION AND DEVELOPMENT, 1996-2001 (Box R3719)
  - SF, AC.2005.019.7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SF 9801 - UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON - BC CONFERENCE: CHALLENGES OF GLOBALIZATION OF INTERNATIONAL RELIEF AND DEVELOPMENT NGOs, 1997-2000 (Box R3719)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2005.019.8; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SI 9704 - (SPECIAL INTERESTS) - BC CONFERENCE: COMMUNICATIONS AND SOCIAL CHANGE, 1996-1997 (Box R3719)
    - SI 9705 - MACNEIL/LEHRER PRODUCTIONS - FISHKIN DELIBERATIVE POLLING, 1997-2000 (Box R3719)
    - SI 9708 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SANTA CRUZ) - "SOCIAL CHANGE ACROSS BORDERS", 1997-2002 (Box R3719)
- AC.2005.021: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2005.021; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3722, R3725, R3726.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.021.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 94022 #7 - NANG'AYO, FRANCIS LEONARD OCHIENG' - BIOLOGICAL CONTROL OF LARGER GRAIN BORER, 1997-2002 (Box R3722)
    - RF 94025 #17 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE: PRIVATE AND PUBLIC COLLABORATION IN CONTRACEPTIVE RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT (BC 95), 1994-2000 (Box R3722)
    - RF 94051 #19 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - BC CONFERENCE: HANDLING INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS FOR VACCINES, 1996-1999 (Box R3722)
    - RF 94057 #60 - ZANZIBAR - EDUCATION (MINISTRY OF) (TANZANIA) - GIRLS' PARTICIPATION AND PERFORMANCE IN SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS, 1995-2002 (Box R3722)
    - RF 94063 #12 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - TASK FORCE ON RECONSTRUCTING AMERICAN LABOR MARKET, 1997-2003 (Box R3722)
    - RF 94063 #15 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - CORPORATE "DOWNSIZING" EFFECTS, 1996-2001 (Box R3722)
    - RF 95001 #386 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC TEAM: SETTING PRIORITIES FOR RICE RESEARCH, 1994-2000 (Box R3722)
    - RF 95003 #571 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (GRADUATE INSTITUTE OF LIBERAL ARTS - CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF PUBLIC SCHOLARSHIP), 1996-2001 (Box R3722)
  - Health Equity (HE) - Dr. Timothy G. Evans Trip Reports, AC.2005.021.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - May 8-9, 1997: Cambridge, MA -Health Sciences Planning Meeting, 1997 May 8-9 (Box R3725)
    - September 26, 1997: London, England -Wellcome Trust, 1997 September 26 (Box R3725)
    - November 10-14, 1997: Uganda, 1997 November 10-14 (Box R3725)
    - November 24-25, 1997: Geneva, Switzerland - Global Forum for Health Research, 1997 November 24-25 (Box R3725)
    - February 23, 1998: Chevy Chase, MD, 1998 February 23 (Box R3725)
    - February 26, 1998: Oslo, Norway - Mrs. Gro Brundtland Visit, 1998 February 26 (Box R3725)
    - March 4, 1998: Baltimore, MD - Johns Hopkins University Visit w/Dr. Robert S. Lawrence, 1998 March 4 (Box R3725)
    - March 26-27, 1998: Geneva, Switzerland -Towards the Better Monitoring of Global Resource Flows to Health Research and Development, 1998 March 26-27 (Box R3725)
    - April 4-5, 1998: Cambridge, MA -TB Meeting, 1998 April 4-5 (Box R3725)
    - April 17-18, 1998: Boston, MA - Harvard Intl. Development Conference, 1998 April 17-18 (Box R3725)
    - May 3, 1998: Geneva, Switzerland -TAG Meeting, 1998 May 3 (Box R3725)
    - May 8-9, 1998: Cambridge, MA - Health Sciences Planning Meeting, 1998 May 8-9 (Box R3725)
    - June 23-28, 1998: Geneva, Switzerland - Global Forum for Health Research, 1998 June 23-28 (Box R3725)
    - July 21-22, 1998: Red Bank, NJ (Staff Retreat), 1998 July 21-22 (Box R3725)
    - September 11-15, 1998: Nairobi, Kenya, 1998 September 11-15 (Box R3725)
    - September 23, 1998: Washington, DC - Vaccines Working Group at NIH, 1998 September 23 (Box R3725)
    - January 5, 1999: Washington, DC - Global Coalition on Immunization, 1999 January 5 (Box R3725)
    - March 18-19, 1999: Geneva, Switzerland, 1999 March 18-19 (Box R3725)
    - March 25-26, 1999: Geneva, Switzerland (WHO), 1999 March 25-26 (Box R3725)
    - April 12-13, 1999: Boston, MA - Development Aid Meeting, 1999 April 12-13 (Box R3725)
    - May 6, 1999: Boston, MA - Harvard Malaria Initiative, 1999 May 6 (Box R3725)
    - May 18, 1999: Toronto, Canada -University of Toronto, 1999 May 18 (Box R3725)
    - June 20, 1999: Arlington, VA - Global Health Council Annual Conference, 1999 June 20 (Box R3725)
    - July 12-15, 1999: Seattle, WA - Global Coalition for Vaccine and Immunization, 1999 July 12-15 (Box R3725)
    - July 22, 1999: Geneva, Switzerland - MMV Strategic Planning Group Meeting, 1999 July 22 (Box R3725)
    - September 1, 1999: Bethesda, MD - MIM Discussions/Gerald Beusch, 1999 September 1 (Box R3725)
    - September 7, 1999: Washington, DC (The White House) - AIDS Convening, 1999 September 7 (Box R3725)
    - September 8, 1999: Geneva, Switzerland -Informal Consultation on Health, 1999 September 8 (Box R3725)
    - September 28, 1999: Boston, MA (Lecture at Harvard), 1999 September 28 (Box R3725)
    - October 14-15, 1999: Paris, France - Drugs for Communicable Diseases, 1999 October 14-15 (Box R3725)
    - October 28-November 2, 1999: Chile, 1999 October 28-November 2 (Box R3725)
    - November 22, 1999: Boston, MA (The Bell Lecture), 1999 November 22 (Box R3725)
    - January 5, 2000: London, England - MMV CEO Meeting, 2000 January 5 (Box R3725)
    - February 6-8, 2000: South Africa - TB Meeting, 2000 February 6-8 (Box R3725)
    - March 22, 2000: Geneva, Switzerland -Foundation Council Meeting, 2000 March 22 (Box R3725)
    - April 19, 2000: San Francisco, CA - Maxygen Meeting, 2000 April 19 (Box R3725)
    - April 27-28, 2000: Washington, DC - CICCR's Strategic Advisory Board, 2000 April 27-28 (Box R3725)
    - May 8-9, 2000: Seattle, WA - Gates Meeting, 2000 May 8-9 (Box R3725)
    - June 26-27, 2000: Geneva, Switzerland - Social Development, 2000 June 26-27 (Box R3725)
    - June 29-30, 2000: Havana, Cuba -International Society for Equity in Health, 2000 June 29-30 (Box R3725)
    - August 17-20, 2000: South Africa (Equity Gauge Conference), 2000 August 17-20 (Box R3725)
    - September 27-29, 2000: Dakar, Senegal - AIDS Meeting, 2000 September 27-29 (Box R3725)
    - October 10-13, 2000: Bangkok, Thailand -Global Forum for Health Research, 2000 October 10-13 (Box R3725)
    - October 14, 2000: Bangkok, Thailand - Alliance for Health Policy and Systems Research, 2000 October 14 (Box R3725)
    - October 30-31, 2000: San Francisco, CA - Biotech Foundation Idea, 2000 October 30-31 (Box R3725)
    - November 14, 2000: Boston, MA - APHA Meeting, 2000 November 14 (Box R3725)
    - January 2001: India - Shantha Biotechnics, 2001 January (Box R3726)
    - February 26, 2001: London, England - Child Poverty Conference, 2001 February 26 (Box R3726)
    - February 26-March 2, 2001: Africa -Decentralization/Equity Gauge Meeting, 2001 February 26-March 2 (Box R3726)
    - March 8, 2001: Washington, DC - Microbicides Workshop, 2001 March 8 (Box R3726)
    - March 15-16, 2001: San Francisco, CA - California Wellness Foundation, 2001 March 15-16 (Box R3726)
    - April 18, 2001: Kampala, Uganda - PHSWOW Meeting, 2001 April 18 (Box R3726)
    - April 18-20, 2001: Kampala, Uganda - AIDS Care in Africa, 2001 April 18-20 (Box R3726)
    - April 23-24, 2001: Europe - Microbicides Euro-Tour, 2001 April 23-24 (Box R3726)
    - May 6-8, 2001: Vevey, Switzerland - Experts Meeting/AIDS, 2001 May 6-8 (Box R3726)
    - May 9-11, 2001: London, England - AIHP Meeting, 2001 May 9-11 (Box R3726)
    - May 28-30, 2001: Sydney, Australia - Diversity in Health, 2001 May 28-30 (Box R3726)
    - May 30, 2001: Washington, DC (several meetings), 2001 May 30 (Box R3726)
    - June 4-8, 2001: Cuemavaca, Mexico (PARO/WHO Conference), 2001 June 4-8 (Box R3726)
    - June 19, 2001: Geneva, Switzerland (Microbicides Briefing Meeting), 2001 June 19 (Box R3726)
    - July 5-6, 2001: Cambridge, England (St. Catherine's College) Paper: Public-Private Partnerships in Global Health. TCE AND LCC., England (St. Catherine's College) Paper July 5-6 (Box R3726)
    - July 19, 2001: Long Branch, NJ - C AND C Staff Retreat, 2001 July 19 (Box R3726)
    - September 21, 2001: Ottawa, Canada - Microbicides and Health, 2001 September 21 (Box R3726)
    - October 18, 2001: Deerfield, IL (Global Health Council), 2001 October 18 (Box R3726)
    - November 1-3, 2001: Boston, MA -Road Traffic Accidents, 2001 November 1-3 (Box R3726)
    - December 19, 2001: Washington, DC - The World Bank, 2001 December 19 (Box R3726)
    - January 14, 2002: New Haven, CT - Yale University, 2002 January 14 (Box R3726)
    - January 31 -February 1, 2002: Washington, DC -PHRplus TAG Meeting, 2002 January 31 -February 1 (Box R3726)
    - February 7, 2002: Philadelphia, PA - Biosyn, 2002 February 7 (Box R3726)
    - February 25, 2002: Boston, MA Harvard Health Caucus, 2002 February 25 (Box R3726)
    - February 27-March 1, 2002: Geneva, Switzerland (SPRG/WHO), 2002 February 27-March 1 (Box R3726)
    - April 9-10, 2002: Toronto, Canada (WHO Meeting on Collaboration), 2002 April 9-10 (Box R3726)
    - April 10, 2002: Toronto, Canada - John R.Evans Event and WHO Meeting, 2002 April 10 (Box R3726)
    - April 20, 2002: Toronto, Canada - Pre-GS Meeting, 2002 April 20 (Box R3726)
    - May 12-15, 2002: Antwerp, Belgium - Microbicides 2002, 2002 May 12-15 (Box R3726)
    - June 3-5, 2002: Geneva, Switzerland - Capacity Building Workshop, 2002 June 3-5 (Box R3726)
    - June 24-28, 2002: San Francisco, CA (RF Office) Health Equity Meeting, 2002 June 24-28 (Box R3726)
    - July 25, 2002: London, England - Access to Medicine Third Meeting, 2002 July 25 (Box R3726)
    - August 22-27, 2002: Johannesburg, South Africa - Stakeholder Forum, 2002 August 22-27 (Box R3726)
    - October 27-30, 2002: Ottawa, Canada - Poverty, Health and Equity, 2002 October 27-30 (Box R3726)
    - November 4, 2002: Washington, DC - The World Bank w/ Jozef Ritzen, 2002 November 4 (Box R3726)
    - January 29-31, 2003: Nairobi, Kenya - Africa Program Workshops 2003, 2003 January 29-31 (Box R3726)
    - February 3-4, 2003: Washington, DC - Action Plan for Health-Related MDGs, 2003 February 3-4 (Box R3726)
    - February 16-21, 2003: Bangkok, Thailand - Impact of Global Issues on Women and Children, 2003 February 16-21 (Box R3726)
    - April 13-16, 2003: Haiti - Harvard Medical School Meeting, 2003 April 13-16 (Box R3726)
    - May 8-9, 2003: Annecy, France - JLP WG 3 Workshop, 2003 May 8-9 (Box R3726)
    - June 9-13, 2003: Bangladesh - Securing the Health of the Poor, 2003 June 9-13 (Box R3726)
- AC.2005.028: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1986-2004; AC.2005.028; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3720, R3721, R3723, R3724.
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2005.028.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SI 9709 - KRISHNAMURTI FOUNDATION INDIA - EDUCATION KIT PROJECT, 1995-2002 (Box R3720)
    - SI 9808 - OLIVETTI FOUNDATION (ITALY) - ANALYZE LINKAGE OF AMERICAN FOUNDATIONS IN EUROPE, 1997-2001 (Box R3720)
    - SI 9810 - INDIANA UNIVERSITY - KINSEY INSTITUTE FOR RESEARCH IN SEX, GENDER, AND REPRODUCTION, 1997-2002 (Box R3720)
    - SI 9817 - FOUNDATION CENTER - LIBRARY AND OFFICE RENOVATION, 1998-2001 (Box R3720)
    - SI 9915 - ECONEWS AFRICA (KENYA) - COMMUNITY MEDIA PROGRAM, 1999-2002 (Box R3720)
    - SI 9917 - GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY - SOCIAL MARKETING IN THE DEVELOPING WORLD, 1999-2003 (Box R3720)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.028.2; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - RF 89050 - BELLAGIO SERIES ON THE ENVIRONMENT - CONFERENCES, 1989-1991 (Box R3721)
    - RF 89050 #13 - (GLOBAL ENVIRONMENT) - BC CONFERENCE: FUTURE DIRECTIONS FOR LEAD, 1997-1998 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93022 #208 - UNIVERSITE CATHOLIQUE DE BUKAVU (ZAIRE) - TRIPLOI DIZATION AS WAY OF BREEDING CONTROL IN TILAPIA CULTURES, 1992-2002 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93022 #219 - CENTRAL DRUG RESEARCH INSTITUTE (INDIA) - LYMPHATIC FILARIASIS, 1993-2002 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93022 #222 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR ZHENG KANGLE, 1994-2004 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93022 #223 - INDIAN AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR KAUSHAL C. BANSAL, 1993-2002 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93022 #230 - PEKING UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR ZHU YUXIAN, 1997-2002 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93042 #31 - AMERICAN MOSQUITO CONTROL ASSOCIATION - SPANISH LANGUAGE SYMPOSIUM TO PROMOTE SCIENTIFIC EXCHANGE AND COLLABORATION, 1997-1999 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93063 - REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY - DEVELOPING COUNTRIES SCIENTISTS SUPPORT, 1978-1993 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93063 #81 - DEVI AHILYA UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - IMPLANTATION PROJECT, 1997-2004 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93063 #82 - BEIJING MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - WATER CHANNEL AND CARBONIC ANHYDRASE GENES INTERACTION IN MALE CONTRACEPTION, 1998-2002 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93063 #84 - GAUHATI UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - STATUS OF WOMEN IN URBAN AREAS OF ASSAM, 1995-2003 (Box R3721)
    - RF 93065 #63 - SULTAN, DAWOOD H. - RE-ENTRY GRANT: EFFECTS OF MATERNAL EDUCATION ON CHILD NUTRITION, 1994-2000 (Box R3721)
    - RF 94011 #20 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS (FRANCE) - BC TEAM: AFRICAN MUSEUM TRAINING PROFESSIONALS, 1995-1997 (Box R3721)
    - RF 95012 - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATION FOR RESEARCH ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1986-1999 (Box R3723, Box R3724)
    - RF 95012 - INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATION FOR RESEARCH ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1999 (Box R3723, Box R3724)
- AC.2005.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2004; AC.2005.039; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3727, R3728, R3733, R3734
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.039.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 95020 #96 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - PREVENTION HIV/AIDS THROUGH PROMOTION OF REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN MYANMAR, 1995-2001 (Box R3727)
    - RF 96003 #575 - UNIVERSITY OF BUENOS AIRES (ARGENTINA) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (MUSEO ETNOGRAFICO), 1996-2003 (Box R3727)
    - RF 95021 #40 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - BC CONFERENCE: COMPARATIVE ASPECTS OF ACCESS TO REPRODUCTIVE DRUGS AND DEVICES, 1995-1999 (Box R3727)
    - RF 95021 #41 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM IN CONTRACEPTIVE TECHNOLOGY RESEARCH, 1995-2001 (Box R3727)
    - RF 95022 #688 - MAINA, GODFREY GITOGO - ADIA: EFFECT OF HABITAT FRAGMENTATION ON BIRD COMMUNITIES IN KENYA, 1997-2004 (Box R3727)
    - RF 95023 #32 - JERUSALEM INSTITUTE FOR ISRAEL STUDIES (ISRAEL) - BC CONFERENCE: COMMON CULTURAL VALUES IN JUDAISM AND ISLAM, 1995-2001 (Box R3727)
    - RF 96001 #506 - INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY (VIETNAM) - DROUGHT RESISTANCE IN UPLAND RICE, 1997-2002 (Box R3727)
    - RF 96003 #578 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (W.E.B. DU BOIS INSTITUTE FOR AFRICAN-AMERICAN RESEARCH), 1996-2002 (Box R3727)
    - RF 96003 #580 - LAKEHEAD UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - RESIDENT HUMANITIES FELLOWSHIPS AT NATIVE PHILOSOPHY PROJECT, 1993-2002 (Box R3727, Box R3728)
    - RF 96003 #580 - LAKEHEAD UNIVERSITY (CANADA) - RESIDENT HUMANITIES FELLOWSHIPS AT NATIVE PHILOSOPHY PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2002 (Box R3727, Box R3728)
    - RF 96003 #583 - COLUMBIA COLLEGE (CHICAGO) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR BLACK MUSIC RESEARCH), 1994-2002 (Box R3728)
    - RF 96008 #82 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - INTEGRATION OF FORAGE LEGUMES IN FOOD PRODUCTION, 1994-2002 (Box R3728)
  - Health Equity (HE) - Areil Pablos-Mendez Trip and Meeting Files, AC.2005.039.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - July 9-10, 1998: Geneva, Switzerland - TB Meeting, 1998 July 9-10 (Box R3733)
    - July 31, 1998: Geneva, Switzerland - WHO, 1998 July 31 (Box R3733)
    - August 26-28, 1998: - San Francisco, CA - TB Vaccine Development and Evaluation, 1998 August 26-28 (Box R3733)
    - September 28-30, 1998: Cancun, Mexico - LatinCLEN IV, 1998 September 28-30 (Box R3733)
    - November 18-20, 1998: Vietnam - DOTS Implementation, 1998 November 18-20 (Box R3733)
    - January 28-29, 1999: - New York City - Public-Private Partnerships Meeting at RF (Biotech/Pharm), 1999 January 28-29 (Box R3733)
    - May 13, 1999: Arlington, VA - Workshop on Expanded Response to TB, 1999 May 13 (Box R3733)
    - July 5-6, 1999: Boston, MA - DOTS-Plus Initiative Meeting, 1999 July 5-6 (Box R3733)
    - November 19, 1999: Washington, DC - Expert Panel on Vaccines, 1999 November 19 (Box R3733)
    - November 29-30, 1999: Geneva, Switzerland - WHO Meeting, 1999 November 29-30 (Box R3733)
    - December 5-7, 1999: Cold Spring Harbor, NY - Vaccines for Developing Economies, 1999 December 5-7 (Box R3733)
    - January 17, 2000: Washington, DC - Research and Development for TB Meeting, 2000 January 17 (Box R3733)
    - February 6-8, 2000: Cape Town, South Africa - Research and Development for TB Drugs, 2000 February 6-8 (Box R3733)
    - February 9-11, 2000: Geneva, Switzerland - Scientific Working Group on TB, 2000 February 9-11 (Box R3733)
    - February 18-21, 2000: Carmel Valley, CA - Global Health Forum, 2000 February 18-21 (Box R3733)
    - February 25, 2000: Washington, DC (The White House) - Millennium Vaccine Initiative, 2000 February 25 (Box R3733)
    - March 1, 2000: London, England -UN AIDS in Africa Partnership, 2000 March 1 (Box R3733)
    - June 13-14, 2000: Oslo, Norway - GAVI Board Meeting, 2000 June 13-14 (Box R3733)
    - August 9-11, 2000: Nairobi, Kenya - Regional Inter-Ministerial Meeting on HIV/AIDS, 2000 August 9-11 (Box R3733)
    - September 4-5, 2000: Geneva, Switzerland - Harmonization for Clinical Development, 2000 September 4-5 (Box R3733)
    - September 12, 2000: New York City - AIDS Meeting at RF, 2000 September 12 (Box R3733)